stuffer31.com 2015-12-27

# Stuffer31 :: stuffer31.com - PRIVACY POLICY

    STUFFER31, INC. PRIVACY POLICY
    Effective as of March 29, 2009
    
    This Privacy Policy applies to Stuffer31 Inc.'s and Stuffer31.com, Inc.'s
    (collectively, "Stuffer31") family of websites (the "Sites"). These include
    Stuffer31.com; vids.stuffer31.com; and any other sites at which this Policy
    appears.
    This Policy explains what information we collect about you and what we do
    with it. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, and we will
    notify you of any material changes to the Policy by posting the new Policy
    hereand changing the "Effective Date" at the top. We encourage you to check
    this page periodically for any changes. By using or navigating any of the
    Sites, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be bound
    by this Policy or any modified Policy as posted. If you do not agree to
    these terms, please do not use or visit any of our Sites.
    
    What information do we collect?
    
    We collect personal information that you provide to us such as your name,
    e-mail address, street address and telephone number. We also collect credit
    card information from you. We generally collect this personal information on
    our registration and order forms when you sign up to receive products or
    services from any of our Sites.
    
    We collect IP addresses and may use this data to analyze traffic to our
    Sites.
    
    What do we do with the information we collect?
    
    We use personal information and other demographic or profile information you
    provide to us to fulfill your order or request; to provide you with
    information about Stuffer31; and to contact you when necessary.
    
    Personal information collected on the Sites is stored and processed in the
    United States and by using any of the Sites, you consent to any such
    transfer of information outside of your country.
    
    Do we share the information we collect with third parties?
    In some cases, we will share information we collect (including personal
    information or anonymous demographic information) with third party service
    providers to manage certain aspects of the services we provide, such as
    maintaining our servers and processing or fulfilling orders for products and
    services you purchase through the Sites.
    
    We may also disclose your information in special cases if required to do so
    by law, court order or other governmental authority or when we believe in
    good faith that disclosing this information is otherwise necessary or
    advisable, including, for instance, to identify, contact, or bring legal
    action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with the
    rights or property of Stuffer31, another user or anyone else that could be
    harmed by such activities.
    
    Is the information submitted in public forums confidential?
    
    No. The Sites may offer chat rooms, forums, and/or message boards to our
    users. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas becomes
    public information. Accordingly, you should exercise caution when deciding
    to disclose your personal information and you do so at your own risk.
    
    Do we use cookies?
    
    Yes. Cookies are pieces of information generated by web servers and stored
    in your computer for future access. The Sites use cookie technology to
    enhance your online experience by making it easier for you to navigate
    through our Sites or make a feature work better. Generally, cookies can be
    disabled. However, you must accept cookies in order to navigate the Sites;
    register for our membership Sites and order products from our online stores.
    
    Are the Sites secure?
    
    We are committed to maintaining the security of your information and have
    measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the
    information under our control. All credit transactions occur in a secure
    area of the Site using Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") software to process
    orders. SSL encrypts the information you input on the Sites. In addition,
    all information is stored in a secure location behind a firewall with
    limited administrative access.

#### BACK
